Kapil, tell me what trading ideas will you share
with our viewers today?
Good morning to everyone. So first of all,
last week we had seen that there was
very good momentum in the particular insurance sector
and in that insurance
too, specifically in the non-life insurance
stocks, we saw very good
momentum there, in the government owned
companies, we were seeing very good momentum there,
but right now I feel that there should be some
traction in the private sector insurance company ICICI GI, the stock had
underperformed in the past time, later it had
formed a very good base, after forming the base there was a
breakout, after the breakout, after
retesting, the stock is again
displaying its momentum, so I feel
that we should see a bullish continuation
sign here, so IGI can
buy it from a short term perspective as well as from a positional perspective,
from a short term perspective it is
trading at the level of 14 34 35, so
here  We should buy and keep a
stop loss of 14-155 on the lower side for a very short term
and on the upper side we will see targets
of 1470 coming in. Secondly,
I had observed that the micro
cap stocks and small cap stocks of the
market are currently seeing
more traction in the micro cap and small cap.
And there too,
specifically the auto sector companies are seeing
very good traction.
Not in one company, but there are four to five
stocks where we are seeing a positive
momentum. So I feel
that a sectoral tail wind is
working behind these stocks. So, out of all these
auto sectors, my pick will be Subros,
which will be a positional one. So,
we should buy at the level of 430 and
keep a stop loss of 410 on the lower side and on the upper side
we can see targets of 470 coming in. Let
us also talk to Kiran Jani and Ayush
Mehta about their trading ideas.
See what a great move we saw on Friday.
Tell me Kiran, what are your trading ideas
today? Very good morning everyone. So we will have two
picks, both will be towards the brothers. One is a
platform stock and the other is from
within pharma. So MC will be our first pick. If you
look at the daily chart here, there is
a consolidation after a good rally.
We called it a flag pattern. In Friday's session,
we saw that a breakout is being seen from there. Also, if
you
look at the open interest wise, there is short covering.
Now this is the last week of monthly
expiry, so there are very good chances
that this short covering may continue and
from here we may see a good move to the upside. So,
we will
go long on MCX. The
closing was around 2920. Our target will be till 2960
and we will maintain 2895 as a stop loss
within MC. The next pick will be
Eka Laboratories within pharma.
We have seen that of
late there is a good move within laboratory stocks. You can
see Metropolis.  Take a look at Doctor Lal
and also at Eka Lab. There is
a good amount of money in all these three stocks.
We are selecting Eka from that. If
you look at the daily chart, there is a
consolidation pattern breakout. There was
resistance of 1090 and 1080 above that. We have seen
that a weekly close was seen, so
somewhere here this consolidation
breakout can lead the price upside. We will
also look for a closing around 1090.
Our target will be
1120. We will maintain a stop loss of 1074. There have been
many good rollovers in Fama as well.
Figures and this pack is moving, so
your picks from here also. Now
Ayush Mehta is also with us on the panel. Ayush, please tell us in the morning about your
trading ideas for today. Very good morning, everyone. There will be
two buy calls from my side. The
first stock will be my Bharat Force. If
we talk about Bharat Force, the stock has
reached a multi-year breakout. If we
talk about its daily and weekly charts, there is
a down call.  We've seen a breakout of a sloping trend line.
Plus, there's a study of
Bollinger Bands, whose bands have opened,
indicating a breakout. If we
look at intraday charts,
we've seen a black pattern on the 60-minute chart. So,
I think
we should buy Bharat Copper from here for a
target of 1170. Our stop-
loss here will be 1090. The second stock would be
Hin Copper. If we talk about Hin Copper, there's a
very nice rounding bottom formation on its quarterly chart. A
cup-and-handle
breakout has been observed on the daily chart. The stock has
broken out above cluster resistance intraday and has
placed itself well above all the important moving averages. So,
Hin Copper should be bought from here
for a target of 172. Your
stop-loss here will be 160. The
Ayush Mehta chart often does
n't explain the meaning of what's happening,
but it does hint at which one, especially
if you're a market student like me.
What is the intelligence on the fundamental street
and by mixing the charts, you have made a
very good investment choice. What
trigger do you see for this
investment in it? I am not aware of any.
Look at the current environment that is visible
and the Secretary had also said that we will
not sell at any price, we will work at our own price.
You understand, what he wanted to say was that we
talk like a fund manager, we will not crowd out the
market in OFS or DISM. We will
try to improve the efficiency of PSUs.
Yes, we can extract more profit from them.
Dividend will be received. If there will be more profit, then the
government will also benefit from it.
Retail shareholders will also benefit. Okay, alright, so this is it, let's move ahead
and now we will talk about stocks and
news. Okay, Vaishali ji, that's it.
Vishal ji, what are
your trading ideas? So first of all, I will
recommend ICICI Bank because
as I told you, I am feeling
good about private sector banks. And if
you talk about ICICI Bank specifically, then
a good corrective move will come.  If we
look at the moving average on the daily chart, we will see that the 200-day moving average is well
supported. I think I am ready for a bounce.
So, the trading target will be 950 with a stop loss of 920.
Second, Federal Bank, which has also corrected quite well
and is currently at a
good support level, so a
target of 155 with a stop loss of 143. And the third one I have
chosen from the mid-cup is Sun Pharma
Advance. We will see that it is
coming after consolidation after a long time and it gave a
good close. So, with a support or stop loss of 255, it will be
a positional trade of 300. These three are
my
ranks. So, out of these
three, two are
banking - one is Federal Bank and one is
ICICI. And the other is a pharmaceutical
company or you can say research company,
Spark. This is on your list. Vishali, okay,
calls have come from all of them.
You have received almost seven calls and you
can take advantage of these seven calls today.